(Leonard:)Still can't believe
she's going out with me.
(Raj:)Nobody can.
(Howard:)That reminds me,
I have a bone to pick with you.
(Leonard:)-What?
-You and I made a pact...
(Howard:)...that if either of us
ever got a hot girlfriend...
(Howard:)...that person
would have his girlfriend...
(Howard:)...hook the other guy up
with one of her girlfriends.
(Leonard:)-Yeah, I don't remember that.
-Wha--?
(Sheldon:)June 30th, 2004.
(Sheldon:)Opening day of Spider-Man 2
at the AMC Pasadena.
(Sheldon:)They only had red ICEES, no blue.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you've been with Penny
for like a month and a half.
(Howard:)Where's my shorty, Morty?
(Leonard:)Howard, you can't hold me to that.
(Howard:)-Why not?
-When I made that agreement...
...I didn't think I'd ever have a girlfriend,
and I was positive you never would.
(Raj:)-How come I wasn't part of this deal?
-You had left the refreshment stand...
(Sheldon:)...in order to indulge in your customary
preemptive pre-show urination.
(Raj:)So that's how it works? I have a teeny
bladder and I don't get a hot girlfriend?
(Howard:)Yeah, Raj, that's how it works.
(Raj:)Damn.